Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

first base

Chapter Summary

First base: sharing intense, passionate, open-mouthed kisses, with a mix of above the belt touching.

Chapter Notes

Rewritten as of July 2020.

First base : sharing intense, passionate, open-mouthed kisses, with a mix of above the belt touching.

His head was spinning as he dropped on top of his bed, still fully clothed. He heard a sound close to vomiting coming from the four-poster next to his, but he just laughed. He'd talk to Ron tomorrow, for he couldn't quite trust his legs to support him should he attempt to stand up again.

Harry could never have imagined the day taking such a completely unexpected turn. Of course, he had already made up his mind and was only waiting for the perfect opportunity, whatever that may be, to make his intentions towards Ginny loud and clear.

But starting the day in the sublimely heinous company of the Hogwarts' Potions Master had in no way indicated that, only hours laters, he would succeed in both securing his spot as Ginny Weasley's boyfriend and kissing her until he felt dizzy. And Gryffindor would win the Quidditch Cup, but that was something Harry could feel good about later, much later, when the taste of her lips would start to fade and he’d be able to use his brain again.

And such intense kisses she gave. She was like wildfire, unleashing completely when he held her in his arms, bringing to the surface a side of him he never even knew he possessed (as a matter of fact, he had kissed girls before, if a snog shared through tears ever counted, but never quite like that).

No. It was different with Ginny: she could only trace his lower lip with her index finger and he came undone against the castle wall. And she enjoyed it, oh how she enjoyed making a fool out of him. He could read it in her eyes, that mischievous glint which reminded him so well of the twins. She was a cheeky one, Ginny. But that made it all the more exciting to him; yes, he was drunk on her, so much better than he had imagined.

Rolling on top of the covers until his head reached the pillows, Harry Potter fell asleep with a strong feeling of content woozing through him, coursing through his veins, for the first time the world around him fully at peace.

When he opened his eyes, it was already morning. The sun was up, there was a happy clatter of Hogwarts students rising to their dormitory windows, and a very wide grin plastered on his face. He was love-struck and it didn't even bother him.

"Ouch! Oi, what was that for?" Harry yelped and glared at Ron, who had apparently decided it was a good idea to smack him right between the eyes with a ridiculously large pillow.

Ron rolled his eyes so hard Harry thought they’d tumble out of his head.

"You had that lovesick smile stretched all over your face and it made me nauseous."

Harry wasn’t quite sure what face he was making, but apparently it must’ve screamed ‘confusion’ as Ron jumped right into a little demonstration of his current feelings: he had put out his tongue and started viciously pointing towards it with his index finger.

Harry’s first response had been ‘Lavender Brown’, but reckoned he valued his mental health too much to remind Ron of his own little trysts around Hogwarts. Luckily for Harry’s eyes, and for their friendship with Hermione, that episode of Ron's life was now over.

"Are you feeling well enough to grab breakfast?" Harry asked, nonplussed, quirking a dark eyebrow.

Ron’s bright blue eyes immediately lit up.

"Always. But, oi,” he pointed a freckly finger at Harry, “no snogging at the table, around the table or anywhere near me, mate, is that clear?" Ron plowed on, poking Harry in the chest for better clarity.

Amused, Harry tapped two fingers against his temple, snuffing the laugh that was bubbling in his throat. "Aye, aye.”

After all, he felt generous enough to spare some quality kissing opportunities if it meant keeping his best mate in good spirits. For now, at least.

Sadly for Ron, Ginny did not feel as generous. Sat next to Hermione at the Gryffindor table, she had already finished eating her breakfast, a healthy helping of buttered toast and pumpkin juice.

She dipped her head to the side and her features broke into a dazzling smile when her eyes fell on him. Harry’s heart violently leaped.

Next thing he knew, two arms were encircled around his neck and a pair of moist lips glided against his own right there in the middle of the Great Hall, lingering eyes of professors and student body thoroughly ignored.

Getting a grip on himself, or rather feeling the incense of Ron's gaze, Harry slowly broke the kiss and grinned down at Ginny, heart strumming wildly in his chest. Quickly, Harry shrugged it off as if to say ‘not my fault’, and plopped himself at the table, Ginny’s hand in his.

Her foot collided with his under the table, a hand under her chin as she looked at him sideways.

"Fancy a walk?"

His stomach churned, yesterday’s memories rushing wildly back to him.

"Yeah, alright," Harry answered, absentmindedly grabbing two pieces of toast to tuck them in his pocket.

A little awkward, a little giddy, they shuffled their feet towards the ancient entrance doors, the sound of Hermione elbowing Ron in the ribs and his not-so-silent mutterings following in their wake.

"He's such a git," Ginny shook her head, amused, sun catching in her hair as they stepped into the summer air outside.

Harry was tempted to stretch his hand and wind his fingers through it, feel its gentle silk slide between his fingers. He stopped at the very last moment, hand flying awkwardly to his own rumpled head instead.

After all, they’ve only been together for less than twenty four hours - if that's what they were doing. He was not quite sure yet. They hadn't gotten round to talking much the other day, if he was being honest.

He bit his lip, air floating out of him as her small hand squeezed his.

"He just cares for you, is all.”

"Well, he might as well stop. I won't have any brother of mine tell me who to date," Ginny confidently stated, nose scrunched up in a way that made Harry want to lean in and kiss it.

And there it was, that look of determination on her face that Harry had fallen throughout the year, each day a little more until his pulse was out of control and his thoughts turned into mush whenever she appeared, flowery scent and blazing look and sword sharp wit. It made his stomach do a little back-flip every time he was fortunate enough to witness it.

"So, erm,” Harry coughed a little in his fist, “are we - I mean, we're dating?"

He was surprised to feel a small glint of smugness sneaking into his tone right beneath the awkwardness, the thrill. Was it pride he was feeling? The creature in his chest roared and purred, thoroughly pleased.

"Naturally," Ginny replied as though it the silliest question he could ask.

She smirked and it made him weak in the knees. It should have troubled him that someone held so much power over him so quickly, so completely, but oddly he was happy to surrender.

They reached a particular secluded spot near the lake and Harry felt his girlfriend – and indeed, it was something thrilling and altogether soothing in thinking of her as his girlfriend – pull him down to sit next to her on the warm grass.

"So," he said.

"So," she mimicked.

If he ever doubted that the conversation between the two of them would flounder, all his worries were immediately waived aside: their lines were flowing effortlessly, as naturally as if they had known each other's minds inside out.

How had it taken him so long to notice? Or has it not always been there, just under his nose, waiting for him to finally open his eyes and see?

Gone was the little blushing girl, his best mate's sister; gone was the shy girl who’d never open her mouth around him. Instead, Harry found himself intently gazing at a breathtaking young woman, all confidence and strength in her posture, in her deep brown eyes and set lines of her jaw.

Briefly, he wondered how she could carry herself as lightly as she did, after all she'd been through, after all she'd seen. Bravery was etched in Ginny Weasley's features and Harry thought he might be able to love her for it someday, in a brighter future than the one he feared was waiting for him.

He listened to her abuse Zacharias Smith and his abysmal Quidditch commentating skills and felt curiously relax, curiously at ease as he leaned on a nearby tree bark. Smiling lightly, Harry bent his knees to sit more comfortably and he was pleasantly surprised to see Ginny move to sit in between his legs, rest her back against the inside of his right thigh, her body fitting easily against his.

She carried on, going over the finer points of the previous day's match and Harry caught himself utterly bewitched by the sight of her lips. He’d never before realised how beautiful they were and full, a bruise delicately blooming on her lower lip where she’d always bite it when she searched for the right words.

Ah, and the way they curved when she laughed, the mischief in her smile, he just had to feel them.

So he did and caught her mid-sentence.

Not minding in the slightest, she responded wholeheartedly, her hands enthusiastically flying tug at his unruly hair.

Chapped met tender and warm, their mouths pressing against each other. Easily, she brushed her lips first against his upper one, then against his lower lip and he parted them without really indenting to.

Ginny pursed her lips further against his, as his hand wandered to the back of her head, pulling her in and as close as he could. He was mollified and, for a moment, Harry felt bold enough to try something he’d never done before: he smoothly touched her parted lips with his tongue, tasted them briefly, and immediately sensed her draw in a mouthful of air.

Harry knew he was travelling on entirely new grounds but took her response as a positive omen and an encouragement to continue. The tip of his tongue gently collided with hers and the taste nearly sent him into overdrive. Honey was mixed with pumpkin juice, increasing his urgent desire to explore her deeper, leaving him breathless against her mouth.

Ginny shifted her position for better access and took over his sheepish attempts.

As she took control, Harry felt more eager and excited, and finally he just let go. Her tongue entered seamlessly into his mouth, making him breathe out aloud.

Ginny sighed softly when his trembling fingers started caressing her waistline through her robe. Gently sucking on his tongue, she set his nerves on fire and Harry heard himself gasp and moan.

He blushed as he realised he’d been making the sounds, a silent prayer speedly raised that she’d magically missed it. With a shudder, Harry drew his head back, finally ending the kiss.

***

Both of them were panting hard, Ginny laying flush against his chest. She could sense the delicate thumping of his heartbeat under her palm and smiled. Snogging a red-faced, messy-haired Harry Potter was definitely becoming one of her favourite activities and it sent shivers down her spine.

She was no expert in the physical department herself, but seeing him awkwardly venture to discover her brought a wave of pride and pleasure washing over her. It might have been vain to bask in the validation of what she had always hoped – that she would be his first, that she would be his only; a sudden, curious thought that made her understand something else about her own self: Ginny was possessive when it came to Harry Potter and she wasn't even ashamed of it.

She didn’t balk under the weight of this strange new realisation. Instead, she grinned at him, breathed him in, with his emerald eyes and his shock of dark hair, a faint blush on his cheeks that Ginny knew she had created. Her, her, her and no one else.

It was the first time Ginny Weasley felt like she belonged, like nothing the world would throw at her could ever make her give up this boy, this young man that was holding her so dearly, so tenderly against his chest. They were going to learn each other inside and out, memorise every small detail and overcome their fears together. He knew it and she knew it and they agreed upon it silently.

It was going to be an interesting journey but it was bloody worth it.

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page

Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

second base

Chapter Summary

Second base: hands travel below the belt and refuse to stop there.

Chapter Notes

Rewritten as of July 2020.

See the end of the chapter for more notes

Second base: hands travel below the belt and refuse to stop there.

First time they stumbled upon the unsteady grounds of second base, they were inside one of the more deserted Hogwarts corridors. They had agreed to trudge up to the library together, Harry offering to help Ginny revise for her fast and coming OWL examinations. Or just bask in her presence, really.

"And it was easier than I thought it would be, we just had to -"

But he paused mid-sentence, noticing that he'd been actually walking alone, sadly offering his generous exam insights and tips to no one in particular.

Because apparently, Ginny had stopped somewhere along the corridor and was staring intently at the entrance to an unused annex of the castle wing. Harry could almost see the mischief and trouble-making forming roots and growing at a rather alarming rate inside her beautiful mind.

And yet, he felt ready to jump right in with her, whatever the consequences. Like magic, she had that effect on him, Ginny.

"I don't quite fancy studying right now," she softly said, turning her head slowly to look at Harry with two deep brown eyes. He felt suddenly out of breath.

Harry walked back to her and gently squeezed her hand, heart leaping somewhere up, up to his throat to rattle there fiercely.

"I know,” Harry started, summoning the rational, Molly Weasley-fearing part of him, “but Hermione might do me in if she found out I'm keeping you away from your revision timetable." He gave her a weak chuckle, brushed a stray ginger lock from her cheek.

Ginny just rolled her eyes as if to say ‘rubbish’ and tightly grabbed onto his wrist. Timetables and OWLs were as far away from her mind as they were from his.

"Come on," she said and dragged him past the dim-lit entrance.

"What exactly are you doing?" Harry asked amused, but followed her eagerly. In truth, whatever it was, he wanted it.

"Homework," Ginny shrugged innocently. "McGonagall was going on and on today about how vital it is for one to possess great knowledge of human anatomy should one want to excel in Transfiguration," she went on, a small kind of smile tugging at her lips as she narrowed the distance between them, between their mouths. "And, incidentally, I happen to plan on excelling.”

Ginny whispered the last couple of words against his lips, confidence visibly flooding through her all of a sudden and any conflicting thoughts left Harry’s brain at a remarkable speed, replaced violently by strong, wild emotions; simmering at the surface of it all, Harry felt an undeniable impulse to kiss that small, smart mouth of hers over and over again until her lips were swollen, until he himself could speak no more.

And so he did, a tad more experienced than two weeks before, when they had shared their first proper snog under the willow tree, cosily settled by the lake. Time stood still back then, as it did now, a bubble of excitement, of content and a brilliant thrill, a very taste of life.

Lips pressed together, gliding up and down against each other, his hands travelling to rest on the small of her back, and hers in his messy dark hair. Harry pulled her closer up against his heaving chest.

The distant part of his brain that was still working told him it must be a great idea, a wise move, so Harry dipped his head and, rather timidly, he planted three short kisses on her jaw and another shy one on the side of her neck.

Almost immediately, he found himself pinned to the wall and mentally hi-fived his own self for trying at least one of the things he’d secretly dreamed of doing to her.

Emboldened by his brave attempts, Ginny gloriously drew her lips closer to the sensitive skin of his neck and let out a hot breath of air before she leaned in to lightly suck on that particular sweet spot. And how good it was, how brilliant it felt, and Harry concentrated hard, shutting his lips tight, afraid that any sound might ruin it all.

Ginny tasted the skin there with her tongue, and it was all it took for Harry to spin her round and press her against the wall. Adrenaline rushed through him, clouding his mind, muddling his thoughts.

"Impressive," Ginny smirked and the smugness etched in the curl of her smile unleashed something very new inside him; the old creature in his chest roared loudly and Harry knew he needed more of her.

Mouth clashing against mouth, he felt intoxicated by her and could no longer stop his hands in their enthusiastic quest to discover her body, to map it till all the little details are tattooed inside his brain - and nor did he want to.

Harry supposed he’d feel guilty towards Ron later, when there would be time for that and no one tugging impatiently at the hem of his robes...

He was about to venture as far as to try and graze her earlobe with his teeth, as he had very secretly seen Bill do to Fleur that previous summer, when he had the misfortune to stagger inside a shadowy Burrow sitting room - but, rather inexplicably, something stopped him. It was a sensation akin to bliss and confusion all wrapped into one and Harry simultaneously felt like he might suddenly float out a window or melt into a puddle at her feet.

"I, er - sorry," Ginny spluttered, leaping one step back, her features catching fire as her eyes grew wide. "I - ah, I really didn't mean to," she stammered on, apologetic and frantic and very, very flustered.

Harry blinked at her before it finally clicked, a definition for the wonderful feeling he’d experienced for the smallest of moments faintly taking shape inside his mind: it had actually been her hand brushing the bulge that continued to form uninvited in his trousers, underneath his robe.

"Oh," Harry stupidly replied and immediately blushed just as furiously as Ginny had. Never in his life had he felt another hand wander so far and the sheer thought left him trembling.

Harry truly wanted to say that it was alright, no problem, I’ve been waiting for this all my life, I’m ready and let's just continue, shall we? But annoyingly familiar voices echoed from somewhere along the main corridor and quickly made him curse and reconsider.

"And then he said – oh! Oh, sorry," Lavender Brown and Parvati Patil stopped to a halt and looked towards a very embarrassed Harry and Ginny, still quite incriminatingly close to each other.

Harry felt the tips of his ears ripple through various shades of red as Ginny appeared to focus on actually looking offended to be so rudely interrupted rather than mortified.

Do those two ever walk alone? Do they always have to go round the castle in a pack? And do they have to be here, of all places?

Harry glowered at them, but said nothing. It was really Ginny who recovered first and had enough sense to throw back a witty remark that should’ve had Lavender and Parvati turning straight on their heels and striding right back - if, of course, the love for gossip didn’t trump sense more often than not.

Toning down her dignified pout, Ginny took his hand and marched them both past the two girls and didn't stop until their shrill fit of giggles faded away.

"Too bad they walked in on us," Ginny shrugged, all bravery and nonchalance.

Harry’s eyebrows shoot up into his hairline. He was tempted to ask what would have happened if they hadn't, but a pesky little voice that sounded irritatingly like Hermione's screamed at him to stuff it and let Ginny study.

As much as we didn’t want to, Harry had to agree: OWLs were getting closer by the day and it was more important for her to focus than to cavort with him all round Hogwarts. After all, Mrs Weasley would never forgive him if he single-handedly sabotaged her only daughter's academic records and subsequent career chances.

"Let's get you into the library, yeah?" Harry said, wrapping an arm around her shoulders to very gallantly shepherd her up the stairs.

Ginny scowled.

"Buzz killer," she pouted and stuck out her tongue at him.

Harry thought she looked impossibly cute and he simply had to lean down and kiss her freckled cheek, chaste and short and light years away from what the burning sensation in his stomach would’ve made him do.

Harry was proud to say that the rest of the day was properly spent inside the library, under the direct supervision and sharp nose of Madam Pince.

***

Second time they got close to second base, it was Harry who got carried away.

They both had a short period on Fridays and they both made a point to take advantage of it. So they tossed their robes away and changed into a more comfortable attire, walking out into the grounds to catch a bit of sun after classes. Alone, undisturbed, safely hidden from the rest of the world.

They sat down by the tree that had quickly become their spot. She was wearing a skirt that day and Harry was pleasantly surprised to notice how her freckles weaved up her body, covering not only her face, but also her legs.

His eyes darted up, lingering briefly over the trail of freckles that climbed all the way up her thighs and disappeared underneath the thin fabric of her skirt. The thought of where those splatters and clusters went efficiently erased all else from his mind.

The thought refused to leave his mind even as they engaged into one of their well practiced snogging sessions. Against Harry’s will, the pestering thing seemed to take control of his hand, for he suddenly surprised himself feeling dainty skin beneath his fingers. His heart spun around in its cage viciously.

Harry searched for Ginny’s gaze; he needed to make sure it would be alright to dare.

Ginny quickly looked over her shoulder to check if they were indeed alone and then she nodded. Harry had the distinct feeling that he’d been struck over the head, he couldn’t quite believe it.

Slowly, holding his breath, Harry brushed the shivering tips of fingers up and up, stopping only at the barrier created by the cotton of her knickers.

Ginny bit her lower lip and, trembling slightly, leant back to rest on her elbows, eyes half-shut, studying him from beneath her eyelids. If he hadn’t been so frozen with fear, so overwhelmed by the newness of it, Harry felt it would’ve been enough to set him ablaze and stumbling over her to kiss and touch everything at once.

It was both amusing and arousing, sitting together like that, his hand bunched up under her skirt, their cheeks flushing with emotion, chests heaving. They stared intently at each other for a heart beat and understood they both felt the same way, they both wanted the same thing.

***

"Oh."

Ginny gasped as his fingers touched her through her knickers. It was a gentle, fearful touch, but it made her senses explode nonetheless. It was electrifying.

He tried the same motion again. And again. And again, until she was chewing on her lip and clawing at the ground beneath her. How he made her feel, ah - it was impossible to hold still.

Harry saw her part her legs further and shifted so he would be closer. With one hand supporting her back, he lightly traced the piece of skin at the barrier between cotton and leg, making her draw in another shaky, shuddering breath.

With great care, Harry pushed one finger under the fabric and sensed the heat and small curls resting inside; it made her bury her forehead fiercely into his chest and hold on tighter to the grass she'd gathered in her fist. God, yes.

And then her nerves went instantly numb when he went on to lightly feel her centre. Louder than she would’ve ever intended, Ginny moaned.

"Gin," Harry hissed into her ear, his voice huskier than she heard it before, panting somewhat erratically. "I don't think I can go on much longer.”

Woefully, Harry removed his hand from underneath her skirt.

"It's alright," Ginny breathed, when all she really wanted to say was no, don’t stop, go on, please.

But she could also understand very well what he meant. Shifting, Ginny kissed him tenderly, hand trailing up from the torn grass to caress his pink flushed cheek.

Then she smoothed her clothes and squeezed his hand as if to tell him don’t worry, it had been incredible. He stroked her back in response. They were getting there, slowly moving to a place where they were comfortable in each other's presence, where they could completely relax and let everything else go. The road was thrilling and a sweet kind of torture all wrapped into one.

***

Third time it happened, Harry had been thinking about his next session with Dumbledore, angsting and brooding all throughout the day. The thought was obsessive and the lack of response all the more infuriating.

When was he going to send for him again? What were they going to do? What if something went terribly wrong?

Uh, so many bloody questions and thoughts revolving round his head. He felt anxious, tense, and, try as he might, sleep refused to come. So he dug out his Map and Cloak from his trunk, you know, just in case, and went to the Common Room to search for the little dots marked Malfoy and Snape, glower over them and see what they were up to.

However, though, he was surprised to find another sleepless Gryffindor curled up in the armchair by the fire.

"Couldn't sleep?" Ginny asked, immediately becoming aware of his presence. Her eyelids fluttered open, body shifting to face him.

"Nah, not much. You?"

"Nope," Ginny shrugged and sighed, absent-mindedly massaging her temples.

So Harry went to sit by her, playfully patting her head, a smile of endearment on his lips as he watched her scowl. But Ginny lightly smacked his hand away and easily slipped onto his lap.

"What are you doing?" Harry asked, amused, but shifted so she could sit better.

"Making myself comfortable, of course. As you interfered with my attempt at a bit of kip sans Romilda’s snores, I do believe I'm entitled to this," she casually replied as she snuggled against his chest, rested her head against the crook of his neck. "And you are a better bed than the old one in the dorm," she went on, supplying her arguments with small kisses on the side of his neck.

He could see the contours of her breasts perked against his chest and his imagination instantly went wild.

Perhaps it wasn’t such a good idea to have an impromptu rendezvous when they were clad only in their pajamas.

Or perhaps it was the perfect one, Harry thought as a warm wave rushed over him, starting from his stomach and rolling up his chest, leaving his flesh searing in its wake.

As always when it came to her, there were two very conflicting thoughts battling inside of him: one that told him to take it slow, to play the gentleman and another different one that begged him not to listen.

Lately, the second one had started growing louder and louder, Harry noticed.

Their snogging session quickly heated up, following the path they had already learned by heart: mouth against mouth, small bites, parting of lips, tips of their tongues, the familiar taste that washed over them every time. It was like fire glowing hot inside of them.

Harry felt her nipples harden through her nightdress and groaned, moving his hand to slowly trace the side of one small breast. He pleasantly found that it was soft, yet full, and he added a bit of pressure to his touch. Ginny happily responded by biting his earlobe and sneaking her hand inside his shirt, mapping his skin, his chest, the muscles hiding there. Eyes glued to her, he watched her hungrily, wildly, as she did so, silently hoping for more.

Harry caressed her breasts through the fabric, pressing a shivering thumb against one nipple. He twisted it between his index finger and thumb and immediately hardened as he heard Ginny’s response, the moan breathed inside his ear.

Just like that, all his sense evaporated. They started tugging at each other's clothes furiously, thoroughly forgetting about their very public whereabouts. Godric Gryffindor himself could’ve walked out of the fireplace for all they cared.

Bravely, Harry tilted the collar of her night dress enough to unveil a creamy, freckled breast. He closed his eyes to steady himself and bent his head until his lips parted around her pink, perked nipple. Her hands grabbed at his hair and pushed his head further against her chest and he could feel her squirm as his tongue darted over her breast, lips sucking at it lightly.

Harry switched to the other one, and Ginny shut her eyes tightly. He felt as her fingers wound into his hair, demanding more, pleading for more, holding him close to her chest.

Harry felt her small hand tightly grab hold of his own and for a mad, vicious moment he feared he'd done something wrong.

He studied her face and found a picture that would forever be burned into his mind, stuck on replay to drive him insane, to send endlessly send him into overdrive.

Sprawled on his lap, with tangled hair and biting down her lower lip, Ginny had her nightdress falling down one shoulder, one perked up breast blooming up from it. Vaguely, he thought she was the epitome of beauty.

He felt his palm being guided underneath her gown and that instantly snapped him out of his revery. Although he now knew what this meant as they had been there before recently, testing the waters, Harry’s heart thumped faster and faster, shooting him up towards a dizzying high.

Finally, sheer impulse took over from reason.

"You rather started something the other day and I thought,” she drew in a breath before she could say, “I thought that maybe you'd like to finish.”

Her eyes were now avoiding his, a flush of red climbing up her chest, up her freckled cheeks to settle there.

A little fumbling, a little shy, Harry dipped a finger under her chin to turn her face back towards him. His Ginny was not easily embarrassed, so he could tell by this alone how difficult it may have been for her to voice her thoughts.

Because of course he had been thinking about it too, dreaming about it day and night, where his actions went quite far, where he didn’t suddenly, embarrassingly stop. In his dreams, he could go on until she screamed, until she moaned his name again and again. In his dreams, he pleased her in all the ways she asked him to.

But in reality, Harry had actually fallen into a habit of waiting an additional ten minutes before getting out of bed, to be absolutely positive he had erased all inappropriate thoughts of Ginny before walking into her older brother and also, ironically, his best mate. To Harry, dreams were better than reality.

“Harry, please,” she said and tugged faintly at his hand.

What if reality could finally be better?

So he took a leap of faith, slipping a finger inside her knickers a bit more confidently, breath hitched as she grabbed onto his shoulders, gripping at his skin to steady herself.

Ginny drew in a shuddering breath as his touch slowly moved to cover her, one calloused tip of his finger carefully, clumsily parting her.

"Is it – er – is it alright?" he mumbled, brow furrowed as his green eyes followed her, hoping that he wouldn’t hurt her, that he wouldn’t make a blunder out of it.

"Oh, yes, it absolutely is, don't stop," she gloriously moaned against the crook of his neck.

Encouraged, Harry slid his finger a little bit more inside of her, brushing briefly against her clit. His instincts told him to be gentle and to lightly twiddle his finger around it. Slowly. Easily.

So torturously slow that Ginny moved her palm up unto his and pressed his hand harder against her. He mirrored her and pressed again, this time making her pant a little louder. With his index finger he drew out and then in, repeating the motion until she couldn't keep quiet anymore, until his name tumbled down her tongue in such a way - ah, Harry nearly came undone beneath her.

He felt something wet and hot spill over his fingers and instantly his feet turned to butter, his entire body shivering with unexpected joy, with a kind of roaring pride. It was him that did it, it was his name that she moaned.

But to his great surprise, her palm came to rest lowly on his abdomen and Ginny looked as though she was attempting to gather all her courage and pour it into her next action. She dragged her fingers a couple of times over the exposed skin above his trousers and then, screwing her face into what Harry thought was an expression of pure, beautiful determination, she slid it further inside his trunks.

It was Harry’s turn to gasp, to groan and grab onto her body, small and nestled on his lap, legs dangling down between his, twiddling around his own as she went further.

Ginny wrapped her hand around him, trembling at first and gaining confidence as she continued to travel up and down his length. Harry felt something heavy press down on his shoulders, body curling tightly around hers, teeth grazing at her shoulder to keep himself silent.

The sensation of her delicate skin against his most sensitive one rapidly broke his resolve. In exactly three strokes, his gaze darkened and something inside him was completely, savagely ripped right apart.

Ginny slowly removed her hand from the inside of his trousers, face scrunched as she observed a thick, sticky liquid drip slowly down her fingers.

"Fuck, no - I'm sorry," Harry spluttered flustered, hurrying to apologise.

But Ginny simply grinned at him proudly, puffing her chest.

"I think we're passed that boundary, eh?"

"Yeah," Harry shrugged, relaxing, and gulped down his embarrassment.

He saw his wand on the floor and wondered when exactly had he chucked it there, but quickly decided it wasn’t important. Like a nimble cat, Ginny easily jumped to her feet, allowing him to bend down after his wand.

"Hope I can get this right," Harry huffed, frowning, concentrating on remembering what Tonks had shown him. "Scourgify!" Harry muttered the incantation, pointing the tip of his wand inside his bottoms, hoping very much that he wouldn’t singe or remove anything.

Luckily, it worked and he offered to help her as well.

A great sluggish feeling settled over him and he motioned Ginny for the stairs.

"Let's do this again sometime," she cheekily told him, winking, before they parted ways to their respective dormitories.

"Maybe just not in a public armchair, yeah?" Harry laughed boyishly, hands dipping into his pockets.

"Can't make any promises," Ginny replied, mischief dripping down her tongue as she raised on her tiptoes and kissed him goodnight.

She left him dazed, smiling dumbly in the aftermath of an unforgettable, exciting night.

Chapter End Notes

fumbling teens stumbling through all the bases, a little at a time

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page

Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

third base

Chapter Notes

[Rewritten as of October 2020]

to Bianca,
for a magical 24th

See the end of the chapter for more notes

Third base : mouths join hands below the belt.

Before the mad hunt for Horcruxes began, it was enough for Harry to so much as make eye contact with Ginny and a flood of warm memories would crash mercilessly into his mind, twist its edges, fold them on themselves; he remembered her face, her beautiful face, her lust-filled eyes, and the way the shadows created by the hearth danced all over her body that final night, before Dumbledore had summoned him and all had been forever changed.

To Harry, it was something akin to agony, to knives entering and tearing apart flesh - that was what not being able to hold her again did to him. However, he knew there was no other choice: she had a future before her, whereas he…

But it was better not to think about it, it was safer to forbid his mind to stumble over it, to shatter before the greatness of this knowledge. It was abundantly better to stay away - or he would go insane.

If only he could tell her, if only he could change his destiny.

If only, he was tired of so many ‘if onlys’.

He would catch her gaze lingering on him every once in a while and it would always spike something inside him, electrify his senses and challenge all his instincts. He would catch her gaze lingering on him and he would almost run her way, sprint to the wild beating of his heart, longing to wrap his arms around her, to just feel her. He would catch her gaze lingering on him and he’d swear hard under his breath, viciously promising himself that he would return to her, that he must return to her, and life would finally be different.

Different. What exactly would be different, really?

The thought was laughable, ridiculous, that he, Harry Potter, could ever lead a different life, a safe life, when all he’d ever known was sorrow, despair, helplessness and lies.

Oh, so many lies. How was he supposed to cut through all this bloody mess and make something new out of it? How was he planning to stay alive long enough to see it happen? He was barking and he knew it and so he laughed a bitter laugh every time he found enough reason to shake out of it. And, every single bloody time, the absurdity of it all hit him like a brick on the back of his head, left him dazed and sad and bleeding from the cracks inside his soul.

Today, though, he would come of age - yet another fact rendered useless by the times they lived in. So he was able to do magic legally, great. It wasn’t like he would refrain from cursing Voldemort into the afterlife if he hadn’t been granted legal permission to do so. Wouldn’t it be just the treat of the century to come face to face with the Dark Lord and say “Sorry, mate, the Ministry won’t allow me to do magic, you see. Raincheck?”

The world simply stopped making sense and somehow he was trapped in the middle of it.

And then even more absurd was the way his own voice just came out of his mouth and agreed to follow Ginny into her room.

Ginny. Into her room.

Her room, when he was supposed to stay as far away from her as he could. Bloody fool that he was, Harry cursed himself and cursed the legs that were carrying him after Ginny, like a sleepwalker, like a ragged doll following its master - and followed her nonetheless; that’s how easily she could entrance him, how swiftly she could break his resolve.

He felt like a spectator at someone else’s black comedy. He heard her whisper something and himself reply, saw her laughing bitterly and then closing the distance separating them.

He witnessed it all as if he was the one person in the audience, watched the actors on stage embrace, kiss with fiery passion, never to let go of each other. And then, to create a climax for the drama of the two young, star-crossed lovers, the door on the right of the stage flew open: enter Ron Weasley, big brother and protector. The couple is broken apart and the curtain falls.

Was he really one of the actors in such a demented play? Was he really about to go into battle at seventeen, ready to measure his power with the darkest wizard of all time?

But he did battle and, somehow, even won the war.

Still, the losses were innumerable. The pain was unbearable and he wished time and again that he could exchange his worthless, meaningless life for those precious many who had lost theirs during that endless May night.

After that, Harry found himself in an endless trance, unaware of his surroundings for the first two weeks, lost in black, cold pool of darkness. He had no recollection of being brought to the Burrow, no idea how he ended on its front steps in the middle of the night, completely dressed, wand ready, and Ginny tugging at his sleeve, attempting to pull him back inside the house.

“It’s over, Harry. Do you hear me? It’s over,” she’d say, that blazing look in her face, the only thing that brought him to the living world those days. She had the effect of a tonic and acted like a safety net, flatly, fiercely refusing to let him slip away into his own misery, back into the limbo.

“I won’t let you, do you hear me? I won’t let you leave me again, Harry,” she’d yell and shake him every time she found him staring absently through the living room window in, alone and frightened in the middle of the night. “It’s enough that Mum and George and Percy are - as they are right now and I’d rather go to war all over than let you drift away from me again. Because I need you, you bloody git, you absolute sod, you – you - I need you to be here for me,” she’d yell at him and break down in front of him, shatter to a million pieces on the ground. His soul bled for her.

And that finally got through to Harry. He could finally understand that; protecting his friends, his loved ones was part of him, part of his raw being and he could do that. If Ginny needed him, he’d escape his own sorrow and remorse. He’d make sure to be there for her, to hold her, to keep her safe.

For Ginny was his anchor, the only thing keeping him still amidst these muddy tides and thus he was determined to become the pillar which would support her from now on.

To his surprise, it wasn’t hard slipping back into that familiar rhythm they used to have. With Ginny, ah, she was something else, so confident and strong, so beautiful in her slight roughness; he’d always be mesmerised by her incredible grace, by her sheer will to live, by the stubbornness with which she held on to life.

This girl that had suffered so much from an early age, the little girl that lost so much. It was like she had shed her girly skin and chose to be reborn as a woman of phenomenal power.

And it was her who’d made everyone aware of their relationship by simply kissing him goodnight after dinner, leaving her parents, brothers and boyfriend gaping. It was her who’d made it crystal clear that the time she and Harry chose to spend alone was theirs only and nobody should dare interrupt (which did not sit well with Ron, to be frank). It was her who set the pace now, her who sought him day after day after day to show him that he’s wanted, and cared for, and home.

With Ginny, Harry spent many peaceful moments in the orchard throughout the summer - something seemed utterly unreachable mere months before. But the good brought many terrifying moments too, such as when Ginny and Mrs Weasley had a monumental row, the first insisting that Harry be allowed in her room and the latter bellowing that that was not happening as long as Ginny lived under her roof or until they were married.

“You should take a leaf out of your brother Bill’s book,” Mrs Weasley charged. “He was twenty-seven, not sixteen –“

“I’m coming of age this summer!”

“- when he was married and allowed to sleep in the same room as his wife,” Molly Weasley crossed her arms and glared at her daughter.

Ginny responded by mirroring her mother perfectly, a spitting image of the woman fuming right in front of her, each made of utter force and wit and fearlessness.

Pouting, Ginny stomped out of the house, throwing a petulant ‘yeah, right’ behind her. Harry was left to stare at the ground, embarrassed, and wonder when had the issue of them sleeping together in the same room even came into discussion. He sure didn’t think about it (or not too much, if he was fiddling with honesty) - only someone barking mad would believe that Molly Weasley would approve of her underage daughter and somewhat-son doing - whatever couples sharing the same room were doing.

He cringed hearing the kitchen door slam shut. Harry remained sat on the kitchen chair, not completely sure what to do with his hands or if he should simply let himself out and quite possibly hide under a rock.

But not even Mrs Weasley could control the force of nature that was Ginny. Whenever her mother was busy, Ginny would very conveniently find that she was unable to mend to a series of things. So, naturally, Harry had to be called over to her room to help her move various pieces of furniture or fix a couple of broken flower pots. After all, she wasn’t allowed to do magic and what was a clumsy, underage witch to do when she needed some help redecorating?

And Ginny redecorated, alright. She redecorated Harry mostly, with a love bite here and there, him walking out of her room with his hair more tousled than ever before.

Still, they never crossed the line of first base again for fear of Mrs Weasley’s retribution (on Harry’s part) and because they had discussed actually approaching their relationship slowly this time. They had, after all, all their lives before themselves and could afford the luxury of just taking their time, unhurriedly, patiently, carefully.

It was during one of their patient and unhurried get-togethers in late July when their taking it slow brought them to the brink of third base. Ginny had sweetly asked Harry to help her find something in Ron’s and his room on the uppermost floor and, being the perfect gentleman, he had swiftly obliged. They had climbed the stairs fully aware that Mr Weasley and Charlie, who’d just stopped by the Burrow in between his research trips, were watching them - and they had continued nonetheless.

“Are you trying to have your family do me in?” Harry quirked an eyebrow as soon as she shut the door behind them.

“No, I’m trying to prove that it’s none of their business,” Ginny replied, waving a hand as if to show how little she cared of what her family had to say.

“Understandable, but would it hurt to be more subtle?” Harry huffed, right hand rumpling the back of his head.

“Hark who’s talking,” she shrugged cooly.

“What is that supposed to mean?” Harry asked, slightly incensed. His behaviour had been completely gentlemanly and she knew it.

“Just that I see no point in being a little hypocrite about it,” Ginny struck back, hands on her hips.

“Is that really what you think of me?” Harry said crossley.

“I do when you try to act as though you’re so innocent,” she quickly retaliated, glaring.

“And what makes you believe I’m not?” Harry continued, petty. “I haven’t been anything but appropriate towards you since I came back.”

They glowered at each other.

“I know,” Ginny finally sighed, “and that’s what’s bothering me!”

Harry’s eyes widened - and so did Ginny’s. He could tell that she, too, was surprised of herself, but the cat was out of the bag now and, in classic Ginny style, she would play along and play it cool.

“It – it does?” Harry sputtered, feeling a bit deflated, scratching his forehead. He thought it was what they had agreed upon.

‘Women, can’t ever understand them,’ Ron’s voice sounded inside his head and Harry mentally and very eagerly nodded.

“A bit. I mean, you know, at Hogwarts you just couldn’t keep your hands away from me and now I have to resort to ludicrous lies that, I might add, no one actually believes only to get you to come near,” Ginny explained, her chin held high, clinging to her dignity, holding fiercely on her pride.

“Gin,” Harry chuckled - and it was such a delight to suddenly discover that, for all her maturity and common sense, she could be such a normal teenager sometimes. Harry felt refreshed, light, and absolutely in love with her.

“Don’t you dare laugh, Harry James Potter, or I’ll – I’ll,” she stammered, in search of a good enough threat, squinting her eyes in his direction.

“You’ll what? Bat-Bogey Hex me?” Harry lifted an ebony eyebrow, smug.

He leaned against the wall, all tall and proud of himself, and watched with amusement as her nostrils flared.

The only thing Harry saw before he tripped and fell flat on his back was a mass of freckles attacking him. Luckily, the blow had been cushioned by Ron’s bed and both of them fell on top of it in a tangle of limbs.

Ginny was pressed flush against his chest, as far as he could see with his glasses skewed above his nose. Harry straightened them just in time to notice her close her eyes and part her lips and he took it as a cue to kiss her thoroughly. His heart leaped.

The kiss turned into a full snog and the snog into hands roaming under shirts. He could never quite resist her when she moaned in a husky little voice she made whenever they’d kiss so deeply that his stomach churned - so he flipped them over brusquely.

As simple as that, with a few well placed sensual sounds, she’d hoodwinked him into wanting to take control. Ginny looked up at him, interested, a cheeky glint at the corner of her eye.

So he lifted her shirt just above her navel and left a trail of kisses back and forth, from the hem of the cloth to the buckle of her belt. She writhed beneath him as he swiftly dragged the tip of his tongue over the sweet portion of skin hidden by the belt.

Inhaling sharply, Harry took a leap of faith and closed his palm over the buckle.

“May I?” Harry asked, timid.

“Just stop talking,” Ginny breathed, her eyes squeezed shut and a mess of ginger hair sprawled against white cotton.

Biting deeply into his bottom lip, Harry fumbled with the belt and buttons, cursing his trembling fingers. When at last he managed to have them open, he bent down to plant one, two, three open-mouthed kisses above the line of her pink knickers before attempting to discard her Muggle denim shorts.

Wriggling, she kicked them off the bed.

Harry traced a finger over her thigh, following a pattern of freckles that led up inside her knickers. He couldn’t believe he’d forgotten this small detail - he’d always adored the constellations strewn across her creamy skin, loved every small freckle, wanted to caress every peak and valley of her body. His eyes opened wider and his stomach churned again.

It was a burning desire the way he never felt it before and Harry started kissing his way up the inside of her right thigh, then her left, lingering here and there, dragging his lips against her skin as she sighed and shivered under him.

The flowery scent he’d always linked to Ginny suddenly invaded his nostrils, spiking his senses, tearing at his barriers. So he kissed her through the fabric of her knickers just to be sure he’d never forget this feeling, making it part of him just as slanting his mouth against hers had recently become.

She let a tiny ‘oh’ escape her lips and covered her eyes with her arm, curling her toes and grabbing at his hair as he blew hot breaths of air against her.

Two blistered palms slipped underneath her and Harry gently lifted, feeling bold and shy and ready to do the scariest thing he’d done in his life: he slowly took her underwear off.

Harry’s face instantly caught fire and his heart threatened to beat out of his chest as she covered her eyes and stood, beautiful, before him, the powerful thumpthumping of his very being flooding his ears, deafening.

Harry had no clue what he was supposed to do - or what he was currently doing, actually. He closed his eyes to steady himself and begged his instincts to save him. They had never failed him before, not even in the face of death.

Now, the same instincts told him to start on familiar grounds. He’d done this before and quite successfully, Harry agreed. Bringing his palm against her center, he pressed softly and then a little harder, slipping just one finger carefully inside. She was as warm as he remembered and it pleased him to see ecstasy bloom in her heavy-lidded eyes. He recalled the gentle circles he’d done last time and applied the motion again, going round her sensitive numb, right to left and left to right.

Ginny moaned as a pair of chapped lips brushed down her abdomen and stopped above her curls. She parted her legs for him, and Harry instantly wanted more, so much more, as much as she could give.

Harry drew near her folds steadily, his mouth stopping inches from her, then paused. Rising on his elbows, Harry took off his glasses and safely placed them at the foot of the bed. He then turned back and he caught her gaze and saw her blush sweety and sexy and everything felt more erotic than anything he’d ever done or imagined.

Instantly, there was something wild, bestial, a raw sensuality in Harry’s emerald eyes, something like steel in his war-hardened features. Ginny looked at him and felt as though she was his prey, as though he was preparing to feast on her. She shuddered, as if a hardwire had gone through every one of her nerves and set them ablaze.

Harry gently laid his lips on her warmth and shyly opened them enough to allow the tip of his tongue to glide against her. It snaked within her and slowly parted her. Exploring. Discovering. Tasting and enjoying such sweet honey. He flicked over her numb and she nearly jumped against him, pleasure growing slowly inside both of them.

He did it again and Ginny moaned louder, burying her heels deep into the mattress, clawing at the sheets with her delicate fingers. Her knees bent and the gap between her legs widened, freeing enough space for him to dive deeper inside, as deep as he could.

She wanted to scream, to toss, to turn, to ask for more, more, more.

Harry wanted to sink into her, to taste her forever, to have more, more, more.

A discrete knock on the door.

“Harry?”

His heart stopped.

Were her brothers always going to interrupt their quality time?

“There are some people from the Ministry here,” Charlie’s voice continued. “They want to talk to you.” There was a pause, in which none of them dared move. “It’s really important,” he tried again, weakly.

“Shit,” Ginny spat through gritted teeth and Harry kept his hold on her, the taste of her still on his lips.

Steadily, Harry raised his head - and just as firmly the same rumpled head disappeared again between her legs and Ginny’s eyes rolled from pure delight, from rough, sheer, primal pleasure.

“Harry?” Charlie Weasley tried again, but remained completely disregarded.

Harry pressed his warm tongue across the little bundle of nerves again and again, increasing the pressure with each flick and Ginny f couldn’t hold back her moans and cries any longer. He felt high on her and powerful as he circled his arms around her thighs, savagely pulling her closer, pulling himself deeper within her. Her dainty fingers flew to his dark locks again and she grabbed hard, holding on for dear life. She squeezed her knees together against his temples and Harry felt a rush of heat over his tongue; she’d found the release she was craving for.

Harry raised his head once more and Ginny looked at him through heavy lids, cheeks blushing and mouth open. He was enraptured with her, with the view of him tightly holding her legs, her tenderly parted lips, wet, so arousingly wet as his were with her.

Fuck, he thought. Ginny sighed and licked her lips and Hary shivered over her. There was no other word to describe what he was seeing than provocative.

“Take this, Romilda Vane,” Ginny lazily stated, pleased, and stretched her arms to beat some sense back into her numb body.

A dizzying feeling washed over Harry as he rolled against his back and, happily, he allowed himself to laugh so hard he actually choked. Of all the things she could have said after he went down on her for the first time, this was what she chose.

“I love you,” he told her, dazed, shifting to sit cross-legged on the mattress, shaking his unruly head of hair.

“What?” Ginny’s brown eyes widened, her eyebrows in danger of blending in with her hairline.

It suddenly dawned on Harry that he’d accidentally confessed his feelings for her.

“What?” Harry blinked, the shock on his face mirroring hers.

They stared at each other for a moment, her half-naked, him blushing to the tips of his ears. And then they started laughing, hard, joyful, unburdened laughter. Blissful, easy, unapologetic.

It seemed that they both had a way with words today and they both failed to grasp the importance of timing.

“So much for taking it slow, eh?” Harry chuckled, his fingers twisting with hers.

“I never really wanted to,” she shrugged. “I rather prefer what we have now.”

“Guess I do too,” Harry admitted, grinning.

He yawned and threw himself on one side, easy, like a lazy prey animal, drawing her to him.

“What about the Ministry people looking for you?” Ginny asked, giggling, placing her arms around his neck and planting little lithe kisses over his swollen lips.

“The who?” Harry absently asked, tracing his fingers through her ginger hair.

“Nevermind,” she suppressed another giggle and returned her mouth to his.

Some priorities easily changed after the war.

Chapter End Notes

This is meant to be a birthday present for the impossibly talented blvnk-art (find on her tumblr. now!) and it's based on her drawing with the same name as the last sentence: some priorities easily changed after the war.

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page

Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

fourth base|homerun

Chapter Notes

See the end of the chapter for notes

Fourth base : going all the way; touchdown.

They thought they would never be apart again, not for this long. Of course, the thought that Ginny was going back for her final year at Hogwarts had completely eluded them for most of the summer. So much had been going on. So much was changing and so little remaining the same. The summer had been a whirlwind and Harry could not, for the life of him, remember days. No days seemed to have existed, but only emotions, emotions stretched to cover four months of grief, anxiety, and delirious exuberance. It had no sense, but he was feeling all these; they were profoundly scratched into him, they had become part of his being. He latched onto tranquil memories to keep his balance and sanity. His hours of remorse were punctured by moments of happiness with Ginny, and over his stolen moments with her there were clouds of desperation.

She’d never asked him to go back with her. She could read him like an open book, always deeply understand him, even without speaking. They had their own way to communicate, for they were so alike in mind and spirit. She knew that he could not go back just yet, that it was impossible for him to witness the reconstruction of his first home, that the pain of revisiting the very place where so many had died, had sacrificed themselves would make him go insane. She knew and she never insisted to be accompanied back to Hogwarts, even if it meant living apart for another year. Because nothing was greater than her fear of losing him once again, seeing him stumble, lost in a limbo of sorrow, of agony, of never-ending torment. No, she would bear the months of loneliness and she would return to him. It was as simple as that. She lifted her chin and closed her eyes and that meant her mind had been set firmly on a plan and she would stubbornly see it through. Just like Harry did.

He’d sometimes lie on his back, seconds before falling asleep, and imagine what it would be for Ginny to be back at Hogwarts. She had somehow become even more stunningly beautiful over the summer and it couldn’t possibly be a trick of the mind. Moreover, he was absolutely positive he wouldn’t be the only one to notice it, oh no. This particular thought reminded him of how basically every guy who could still walk unassisted had been ogling her at Bill and Fleur’s wedding, a young, breathtaking girl in a golden dress; how she had received more invitations to dance than she had time to accept, and, of course, how Viktor Krum had wanted to make a move on her. Until Harry did something about it, that is. Oh, yes, he was most proud of his quick thinking and privately agreed with Ron that Krum was only good on a broomstick, as far away from Ginny as possible. In fact, every other guy had better keep his distance or else. Or else - humph. Harry would shift on his side, loudly exhale and crumple the sheets in his fist until Ron would throw a couple of well chosen swear words his way because the noise kept him awake.

Truth be told, he never really had time to linger much over such musings or get too drenched in his own imagination, constructing scenarios where he sheltered her from every man, leading her to publicly proclaim him her Chosen One, because Ginny was always by his side those days, so full of life and surprises. Her boldness inspired him and her laughter made him want to live forever if it meant spending every single day with her, lost in her heavenly smile. The memory of what she did for him on the morning of his eighteenth birthday still gave him goosebumps and he distinctly remembered grinning until his cheeks hurt for the rest of the day. Which, of course, made Mrs Weasley eye her daughter suspiciously, to which she would just bat her lashes angelically and put on an innocent face.

In reality, Ginny had burst through the door at the crack of dawn, giving both Ron and himself a heart-attack and had instructed him to get ready because she was about kick his ass at Quidditch. After which she’d simply slammed the door behind her, leaving Harry clutching his stomach in a wild fit of laughter, and Ron looking harassed and swearing.

He had pulled on a pair of worn jeans and plain black t-shirt, brushed his teeth, sighed noticing his bed-hair and went out to see where his insane girlfriend was hiding. She called him to the broom shed and he wondered what she could possibly be up to so early in the morning, when everyone else was still soundly asleep.

“Happy eighteenth,” she grinned, pecking him on the lips.

“Thanks, but this you could have said inside the house, don’t you reckon?” he chuckled, one hand draped round her shoulders.

“Well, yes, but I want to give you something and seeing that everyone is keen on staying at the Burrow today and my brother’s snores knock all romance out of me every time I enter your room, I figured some privacy would do us good,” she explained, punctuating her argument with small kisses.

“Did you now?” Harry asked, distracted, for her right hand was about to make full contact with the buttons of his jeans. He mentally cursed himself for not having enough sense as to put on some fresh pair of boxers or to take a shower. No, he had to believe she really wanted to play Quidditch and throw on his oldest trousers over the faded pair of underwear in which he slept. Oh well. You live and you learn – never trust Ginny Weasley.

The birthday boy felt a shiver down his spine when he heard the fly unzip. Ginny looked up at him and smirked, then slowly bent her knees until her forehead rested on his abdomen. Could he dare get his hopes up? As her hands started pushing down his jeans, not only did he start daring, but there was even a distinctive victory themed soundtrack that had started playing in his mind.

Not even bothering to blush, he watched mesmerized from above, watched the ginger head get dangerously close to his nether region. A feeling of incredible warm, of lightheadedness engulfed him and he just closed his eyes, resting his head on the wooden wall of the broom shed.

Yes, such was Ginny, pulling him back to life from wherever he might get stuck. Every day with her was something akin to stepping outside into a painfully hard sun, but after your eyes get accustomed to the powerful light, you feel the warmth on your skin and your heart beats faster and you are grateful that you are alive. This was the only way he knew how to describe their relationship, for he was living something more intense than he could put into words. And he was never great with words. He was rather more of an action man. Let others waste their time with beautifully crafted phrases; he was aching to live all of the life he hadn’t lived in nearly eighteen years of existence. And he chose to live it with her – on his birthday, on her birthday, every time they could steal moments for themselves, and in the in-between of it all.

On the morning of September 1st, the Weasleys witnessed a strange phenomenon. Harry Potter was skipping down the Burrow steps, a dubious buoyancy about him. They had all presumed that he would be sulking and moody for the occasion. They could only assume that he was versatile and that was that. But Hermione, seeing him grin like a madman as he walked onto the platform, hand in hand with Ginny, knew better. And, to her credit, she kept silent until she found Ginny in their now shared dormitory, unpacking her trunk.

“So, are you ready to talk about it?” she asked, closing the door behind her.

“About what?” Ginny responded with a question of her own, her focus on the contents of her trunk.

“Would you rather pretend that nothing happened?” Hermione pressed on, comfortably settling herself on the four-poster closest to her friend.

“Pretend what?” she said, fixing her wand behind her ear and bending over the trunk once again.

“Harry was practically skipping this morning,” Hermione curled her lips into a faint smile, seeing Ginny freeze for the smallest of moments.

Taking a second to compose her face and to be absolutely positive that the heath which had crept up her neck was gone, she slowly turned towards the brown-haired girl. She was looking at her expectantly and Ginny knew it would be pointless to lie. Hermione was a superb judge of character when it came to her and she always guessed what was happening inside her mind, sometimes even before she was able to accept it.

“Did you…?” she inquired.

“Yeah,” the redhead acknowledged and she was surprised at the stoicism in her voice.

“And? How did it feel?”

“I’m not sure – I mean, it was fast, and messy, and bloody brilliant,” Ginny breathed, just a little flustered. She took a seat on the bed opposite Hermione, hugging her knees to her chest. “I guess it was rather perfect.”

“I reckon you’re both very happy,” Hermione told her, shifting to rest her back on the bed pillar and stretch her legs. “And I’m happy too. For you.”

“What about you and Ron?” it was Ginny’s turn to interrogate her and she was keen on not missing the opportunity. Privately, she was curious, even though nobody would hear her admit that about her older brother’s love interests.

“Oh, you know, we’ve both been very busy over the summer and –“ the bushy-haired girl rapidly rolled the words down her tongue, as if repeating a well-rehearsed line.

“So you haven’t?” Ginny cut across her stammering. Her friend closed her mouth and paused, frowning.

“Honestly, no. I mean, I was mostly with my parents and - there were some moments and, yes, I started thinking about it after Australia, but something or other would always happen before we could – you know,” she bent her knee and pressed her forehead to it.

“I understand. Well, it’s no big deal. You’ll just have to buckle up and do it because my brother’s too much of a pansy to actually –“

“Ginny!” Hermione chastised her.

“What? It’s true. I know Ron,” she twirled a ginger lock about her index finger.

“Maybe not all that well,” Hermione smiled sheepishly.

“Ew,” the redheaded witch stuck out her tongue. Hermione giggled, suddenly happy that they were able to stress about such trivialities again, that they could act their age again.

Lying awake in the dark room, Ginny sensed her heart beat faster as she reminisced what would forever be one of her dearest memories. The whole string of events played rapidly on the back of her eyelids and she couldn’t help but grin.

It was past midnight when she had heard him descending, his footsteps louder and louder with each story. She had ceased her packing and gone out to see what was wrong. By the look of him, chin down and hands in his pocket, she knew something was definitely bothering him. Ginny casually leaned back on her bedroom door and asked him what was on his mind. He clenched his knuckles harder inside his pockets and made up some cock and bull about seeing if she needed any help. Of course he wouldn’t just speak his mind, he was Harry bloody Potter and his mission in life was to hide every meager moment of weakness. So she’d roll her eyes and bluntly point out that something was troubling him. Thus, they agreed to just talk and she guided him into her room, amidst the disaster sprawled everywhere.

“Finished packing?” he joked, taking in the sight. The floor seemed to be boobytrapped with her school books, while the bed was clustered with robes and every article of clothing she owned.

“Haha,” she scoffed, tossing her clothes and robes unceremoniously on the floor in one go.

Ginny sat on the bed and patted the spot next to her as if to signal that she was expecting him to sit down and start talking. So he did and wanted to say something, but he noticed the way the oil lamp in the corner created dancing shadows in her chocolate brown eyes. That blazing look in her face rendered him speechless, made him completely forget. It was as though the hard feeling clutching at his heart had been channeled into her through the lithe touch of their thighs. He realised he had been longing to see her and she wasn’t even gone yet. He had been desperate to hold her, even though only hours had passed since their last embrace. He had been afraid of the loneliness that he would have to suffer over the long months of separation.

She understood everything, read his thoughts. She shared his misery, his fears, his heartache. Lifting one finger, she pressed it gently to his lips and he lightly kissed its tip in response. Ginny leaned forward and hungrily glued her mouth to his, determined to prolong the moment of goodbye as much as possible. Through the kiss, he caressed her cheeks, her hair, the creamy skin of her neck. She bit his lip with urgency and he eagerly obliged, opening his mouth to meet her tongue with his. They would never feel tired of this dance they were doing, never weary of traveling the lengths of their bodies until they lay naked, completely exposed to each other.

He lifted her shirt and left a trail of kisses on her abdomen, threw the garment on the floor and unclasped her bra. She took it off and arched her back, allowing him press his lips in a stream, from her collar bone down to her chest, to take one nipple tenderly between his teeth and then the other. She grabbed a fistful of raven locks, pulling his head closer to her as his fingers found their way down her trousers and inside her knickers. Ginny brought his mouth to her to stifle the moan threatening to escape her lips at the feel of his index finger inside.

Harry gently pushed her on her back and took off his own black shirt, along with his glasses. Bending over her, he marked her body with open-mouthed kisses. He removed both her bottoms and underwear and she shivered under his gaze. The prey animal was back and he was wild. Wild with lust as he took her in, a delicate, yet powerful young woman with long, flaming red hair, framing her petite figure. He lifted one of her slender legs and kissed the back of her thigh, descending in his path until he reached a mess of ginger curls. She had the sweetest taste, she was his ambrosia. She made him feel immortal.

She nearly screamed when he kissed her there and it was maybe this which made her finally decide. Brusquely, Ginny sat up, startling him. Not bothering to explain, she reached for his belt and shoved his jeans down his legs. Harry watched her, dazed, not entirely comprehending what was about to happen. Ginny battling for control always had this effect on him.

In her haste to free him of his boxers, she nearly fell off the bed. They both stopped and looked at each other, breaking into laughter. Her clumsy gesture had shattered the trance they had been stuck in and cleared their heads of grogginess. They both understood what this was leading to and neither was afraid. They were nearly there and they would walk past it, together, always together.

“Nice move,” he taunted her, his boxers slightly jerked off as to reveal a patch of dark hair and a V line hiding within.

“You do it, if you’re so smart,” she shot back, pouting.

He took two steps back and made a show of taking off the pair of black boxers. He held up his hands as if to say ta-da! and she giggled. The smile lit up her features and all of a sudden he was strongly aware of the twinkle in her eyes and the smirk on her lips, as her gaze lingered on his lower body. He needed her acutely, everything about her provoked him, goaded him until he could no longer stand it. It felt like they have undressed in each other’s presence since the very beginning, their love as old as time.

So he climbed into bed, one knee between her legs, and claimed her lips. One hand supporting him above her and the other caressing her breasts, lightly squeezing them, stroking parts of her body over and over again. She panted as their kiss deepened and encircled his neck with her freckled arms. He moved to kiss along her jaw and brushed one finger over her cherry lips; she lightly suckled on it, flicking her tongue twice over the trodden skin. The sensation made Harry’s insides boil and he painted a wet trail with it, from her jaw, between her breasts, down her flat abdomen and arriving at her warm entrance. Ginny closed her eyes and murmured his name, feeling the wet tip of his finger inside her, pleasuring her, twisting the small bundle of nerves until her body was on fire.

She wrapped her legs round his torso and he removed his finger. His sex was touching hers and the softness of her flesh made him almost delirious. She lifted her upper body to capture his lips, instilling a sense of determination into him. The young man laced his fingers with her dainty ones and pushed gently at her folds. His tip parted her and it was so good, so blissfully good that he thought he might come undone. Ginny whimpered and bit her lip hard to silence herself. She dug her nails into his back and her thighs tightened their hold on his torso. She was ready and she could get through this.

Their first motion was awkward and rash. Leaning on his elbows, he twice caught her hair underneath. She writhed beneath him, unwittingly drawing him in just a little bit deeper, leaving him breathless. He was all readiness and excitement and no stamina. He wanted her impetuously, desired her, he needed her right then.

Too roughly, Harry penetrated her barrier and she cried, sinking her teeth into his shoulder. I’m sorry, I’m sorry, I’m sorry, he would mumble, kissing her eyelids, her forehead, her cheeks, cupping her face into his blistered palms. She filled her lungs with air, and pressed a cheek to his. They sat like that for moments, breathing, just breathing. When he started moving again, she gripped his hand harder. He brought their clasped hands to his mouth and kissed her knuckles dearly, tenderly. If only he could save tonight. If only. He lifted his eyes to the window, towards the start-struck sky and the ghost of an idea cut through the fog in his mind. He’d once told her that the freckles on her body were like millions of stars, strewn across her skin in constellations. He’d told her that if the stars hid all over her body, then the sun hung in her hair. He’d told her she was his universe and she blushed and laughed at his sappiness.

His moves were rough, somewhat irregular, pleasure and pain shooting through her with each thrust. He glided deeper within her and their mouths crashed onto each other, a folly of teeth and lips and tongues. He pushed harder and she entwined their fingers once again. His left hand sneaked up, kneading her breast with a hungriness that made her toes curl. He worshipped her, feeling the curves of her body under his calluses. Oh, how he worshipped her, his fiery girl with hair like the setting sun. Her sweet mouth slightly open, her white teeth revealed, savagely biting her lips in ecstasy until they were crimson and swollen. Her round breasts bounced against his chest, her nipple grazing his skin. It was primitive, profane, like a ritual taking over both of them. He searched for a rhythm, he needed control. Two hard thrusts, one soft. Repeating it, he watched as they were wrapped together, their beings melting into one. Weaving and unweaving. In and then out. Creating magic together. He wanted it to last forever, to be forever drifting in this moment of passion, forgotten in this life changing embrace.

But his body betrayed his mind, working against his wishes and his pelvis slammed harder against hers. Harder, and faster, and stronger, skin bruising skin. Fuck, he thought and buried his head into the crook of her neck. He was no longer in control, they were no longer in control. Adrenaline rushed through their veins, clouding their eyes, their minds. He felt a fire burn inside him, his groans growing louder. Her skin was flushed, her hair a tangled mess. She moaned his name over and over and it was this which made him finally let loose. His vision blurred, Harry felt wonderfully high. A buzz went through the tips of his fingers. It was electrifying.

Diving back from that sweet height, he propped himself on his elbows and looked down at the redheaded girl smiling brightly at him. He brushed the stray lock from her face and pressed his forehead to hers. He tried to find a name for the raw emotion he was feeling, for it made his heart beat madly and butterflies spin inside his stomach. Tipsily, he wondered if the word he was searching for was magic, because nothing else could leave him as intoxicated, as giddy as he was right then.

“I love you,” Ginny whispered in his ear.

Of course, he realised. Love. A magic more powerful and ancient than all. A wide smile was plastered all over his face and he seized her lips again and again, consuming them, pouring all the love he felt into his kisses. He guided her warm palm to the place where she could feel his heartbeat.

“Can you feel this? It beats for you. You’re one in a million,” he softly told her.

Tears formed at the creases of her eyes and she bat her lashes fast to banish them. She feared that, should she allow herself to cry, she might burst from all the emotions colliding inside her. She loved him, she needed him, she adored him, she wanted to always protect him. She would gladly rip her heart out and offer it to him. For the first time in her life, she found that she was lost for words. So she simply held on to him, even after his head fell into the pillow, beside her. They were drunk from such love, forgetting the world around them. For Harry and Ginny, only the two of them existed that night.

In the morning, when he sneaked out and she remained alone, she finally let all her feelings wash down her like a waterfall. She desperately gripped her sheets and melted into his perfume. A mix of wood, treacle tart and earth encumbered the atmosphere and she wrapped the sheet round her naked body, clutching it close to her chest. That night, miles away from the safety of his arms, she fell asleep in the same position, holding his forgotten shirt to her heart and breathing in a scent that belonged to him.

While Harry, well, he had indeed continued to feel dizzy all day, drunk on her and drunk from the recent memories. He had spent the first part of the afternoon in a daze, wandering aimlessly around the Burrow. The feeling was so overwhelming, so great, so unlike anything else, that if he suddenly started floating to the heavens he would not be surprised.

“Bloody hell! What in the name of Merlin’s old nightgown is wrong with you, mate?” Ron brought him back to earth. They were doing the dishes in the kitchen or, rather, resting on a chair each, while the enchanted sponge cleaned the plates and cutlery. Being of age brought along many benefits, you see.

“What – no – nothing’s wrong with me,” Harry’s voice came out louder and squeakier than he’d intended. Sod it, could he exert no self control? Couldn’t he be subtle for once? And to think he dreamed of being an Auror. He imagined himself squeaking in a villain’s face and immediately cracked a mental chair over his head. Mentally.

“I’ve known you for the past seven years and there is definitely something the matter,” the redheaded young man glared at him.

“Yes, well – erm,” Harry rubbed the back of his head. Was he really about to confess to Ron? Was he insane? Was he definitely done with life?

“What? What is so complex that is taking you an entire day to formulate?” Ron asked, annoyed. “Have you been reading Hermione’s books because that is just indecent,” he eyed his best friend suspiciously.

“I – well – you see,” he took a large gulp of air and breathed it out all at once. “Isleptwithsomebodyforthefirsttimelastnight,” he blurted and braced himself for a well deserved older brotherly punch in the face.

“Care to give it another go? I couldn't quite catch it the first time,” Ron said, amused.

“I…I kind of slept…,” he tried again. Seeing Ron stare at him, Harry was ready to give all the gold left in his vault only to be taken away from that chair in the Burrow’s kitchen, where he was slowly but surely tortured to insanity by his oblivious best mate.

“You overslept? Blimey, did Mum catch you? You know how she gets when she expects us to do stuff and –“

“No! Give me some time to find my words,” he gushed, frustrated.

As if to indicate that enough time had passed already, Ron dramatically took out his watch and pretended to check it. The dark-haired boy rolled his eyes and attempted to steady himself once again. He had to get this over with before his nerves betrayed him.

“Alright, so…Remember that you are my best mate, yeah?” he started.

“Course I am and I’m also afraid that you’re barking.”

“And that we promised to be friends no matter what.”

“Alright, that’s it, I’m freaked out.”

Before Ron could add anything else, Harry held up his hand and drew in another mouthful of air. “I slept with Ginny last night,” he spoke, trying to void his words of all emotion.

Ron blinked. Once. Twice. Three times. Maybe if he pinched himself, the vision of Harry confessing that he'd slept with his little sister would go away. He pinched so hard tears formed at the corners of his eyes.

“You what now?”

Chapter End Notes

They finally got there, together. And it's a good thing they did because there might not be much of Harry left after Ron's done with him, huh?

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page

Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

managerial ejection: a sequel

Chapter Summary

Sequel to touchdown, in which Harry and Ron tipsily discuss private affairs.

Chapter Notes

See the end of the chapter for notes

Managerial ejection: the umpire has the right to toss the manager off the pitch; the manager may not touch, spit on, insult or shout at the umpire.

 “Mate, don’t get so pumped up –“

“Don’t you tell me what to do! You bloody traitor, you –“

“Ron, keep it down! Your Mum might hear and –“

“Let her hear! Maybe she’ll throw you out, like you deserve –“

“Oi! If you want me gone, I’m gone!”

They were both standing up now, chairs kicked aside. A million shades of red on his face, Ron was breathing hard, knuckles white from clutching his wand tightly. Across from him, Harry was torn between shoving a fork up his best mate’s flaring nostrils or just leaving immediately. Privately, he marveled at his own innocence in thinking that Ron might take this information nicely. Calmly. But then again, this was the person who threw tantrums for weeks because Hermione dared kiss another guy at one point in her life. Reason was not his finest point, and Harry would just have to step up and be the adult of the two. Or just give him a good smack, either one would do.

“Look, last year was different and bottom line is I’m not leaving her ever again. We’re both very serious about this and it’s not like I had it planned –“ he started to explain, trying hard not to grit his teeth. Unfortunately, Ron snorted halfway through his discourse and Harry had to dig his heels hard into the ground to stop himself from sprinting over to the redhead and bitchslapping him.

“What? You don’t believe me?” he asked, incensed.

“No, I don’t,” Ron spat.

Their eyes shot hexes and curses at each other. Harry had a vision of his younger self, throwing a POTTER STINKS badge flush into Ron’s throbbing forehead. He sighed. Ron might’ve had his pants in a twist, but he was still his best mate and he hated fighting with him.

“I know she’s your little sister –“

“YOU HAVE BESMIRCHED MY SISTER!” he bellowed, turning maroon.

Besmirched? Besmirched?! Who still uses this word? Gormless prats like Ron, that’s who. Harry growled to himself, having enough sense to silently cast Muffliato just in case any extra Weasley decided to join in on their merry conversation.

“Aren’t you getting a bit beyond yourself?” Harry cocked an eyebrow.

“DO NOT BLOODY TELL ME WHAT TO BLOODY DO, HARRY BLOODY POTTER! YOU TRAITOR, YOU FAKE FRIEND, YOU – YOU –“ Ron roared. “You stay away from my sister,” he added, almost in a whisper. His eyes turned to slits, his wand pointed in the young man’s direction.

“No,” Harry’s jaw was steeled. He was swiftly slipping into his stubborn persona, the one that would not rest until the plan was accomplished, until the goal was reached. And now the goal was to make the lunatic howling across from him understand that his relationship with Ginny was very serious and very much their business, even if he had to somehow insert this information into his skull.

For a moment, he thought Ron would throw him out and, privately, Ron really did ponder it. But then, something in Harry’s iron gaze made him remember the skinny, messy-haired child, with his glasses heavily wrapped in sellotape, a poor excuse for fixing them, and he knew he could not stoop so low. Harry was more than a brother and he had been since day one. He dropped his gaze, anger and confusion mixing inside his chest. He’d been brought up to care for and protect his little sister. But now that his best friend was involved, didn’t she still need caring and protecting? If he were to be honest, there was no other bloke he’d like to see Ginny with, so why did he react the way he did?

“I’m going up,” Ron mumbled and turned on his feet to leave.

Harry followed the mane of red hair disappear up the Burrow’s top landings. Cursing under his breath, he swung a hateful kick at his former chair. Sadly, the action brought him no vindication, but tears of pain and a searing panic that he might have broken his toe.

Using his wand, he lifted and straightened his chair, then collapsed into it. His head hurt from all the pent up frustration, and he pressed the tips of his fingers hard into his forehead. If only he could just throw a punch up Ron’s freckled face, he would definitely feel better. If only he could have kept his mouth shut. If only –

His train of thought was interrupted by a rustle of footsteps. Through his parted fingers, he saw his best mate’s dirty old sneakers descend towards him and he prepared for another round, possibly for a physical fight. He knew both of them had to blow off steam somehow.

Instead, Ron flung a heavy bottle of auburn liquid on the table, one that Harry recognized as Ogden’s Old Firewhisky. He looked up at Ron in surprise, wordlessly asking what that was all about.

“Mum and Dad are over at Bill’s,” he shrugged and drew his chair closer to the kitchen table. Without sparing Harry a glance, he tapped the lid with his wand and poured two glasses full of the burning liquid. One he grabbed for himself and the other he pushed to the other side of the table, to the dark-haired young man who was still gaping at him.

“Start talking,” he commanded.

“What?” Harry asked. He was still not catching on and everything he knew about the ginger boy told him this should not be happening. Instead, they should either continue their quarrel or retreat and avoid each other for days.

“You heard me. Drink and start talking,” Ron said coolly. Glaring at Harry, he took the first gulp and relaxed against his chair, sensing the sweet taste of the alcohol enveloping him. He had no palpable experience with drinking, but neither did Harry. Therefore, he was determined to outlast his friend and get the truth out of him.

The lightning on his forehead faintly prickled as he started draining his own glass. Wiping the corners of his mouth with the back of his hand, he caught a glimpse of the old scar, an aftermath of his scuffle with the old hag, Umbridge. I must not tell lies, it read. Fine. He won’t. If Ron wanted him to talk, then talk he will. No details spared, not even if Ron begged him to shut up.

“I couldn’t sleep,” he started, filling his glass once again. “I couldn’t sleep because I kept thinking that she’d be gone in the morning and we wouldn’t see each other for months.”

Ron frowned. He had been battling the same thoughts, and, if it weren’t for Hermione’s strict instructions that he shouldn’t come barging down her front door in the middle of the night, especially when her parents were home, he would have gone flying by her side.

“So I went downstairs to see how she was doing, maybe help her pack, if she needed any help,” he continued, and, hearing Ron’s muffled snort, he added “I’m serious, mate. I never thought that we would – you know,” he stared at his Firewhisky intensely, avoiding his friend’s burning gaze.

“Go on,” Ron heaved his chin as if to indicate the interview was not over yet.

“So I went in,” Harry scratched the back of his head, staling. “Everything was a mess and – and I reckon I haven’t drunk enough to tell you this.” He felt his ears catching fire at the memories and he silently prayed that he would not start grinning like a moron. He was still over the moon with joy, mind you, but now was not the time to show it.

“Then drink. Come on now, bottoms up,” Ron replied and clinked Harry’s full glass with his own. Both boys poured the liquid down their throats, heads leaned backwards. The glasses were refilled and once again they emptied them in one gulp. Three Firewhisky shots later, the dark-haired – and slightly inebriated wizard – felt he was confident enough to continue the story.

“She was so beautiful and had that blazing look, you know, almost like your Mum when she gets angry,” he explained, an amused expression on his face as he took another swig of alcohol.

“Oi, don’t you bring my Mum into this,” Ron threatened, stumbling upon his words.

“Sorry,” Harry giggled. Somewhere in the back of his mind, he was scandalized at his giggling. Giggling was not Harry Potter’s thing, no, sir.

Ron brought his fist to his cheek to support his head, propping his elbow into the table. If he concentrated hard enough, he two Harrys that sat in front of him would stop spinning. One of them poured another glass of Firewhisky and he heard himself command that they drink it immediately.

“She was looking at me in a way that I believe is so – so sexy,” he continued as his friend’s head hit the table in a failed attempt to show his disgust. “So we started undressing,” Harry hiccupped. “And she tried shoving my pants off and nearly fell off the bed,” he laughed, slapping his knee. Ron howled in equal tones of laughter, the image of his sister rolling off the mattress in an attempt to – erm – disrobe his best mate appearing suddenly very amusing.

“Then I was on top and I was very gentle,” he nodded to no one in particular, grasping for his glass and draining it once again.

“You fucking git, I’ll murder you,” Ron cried in drunken rage and tripped over the legs of his chair. Harry laughed harder, seeing his best mate crumpled on the floor. In his fit of laughter, he hadn’t noticed that he was leaning much too hard on his own chair, thus ending up with his back against the cold ground. Out of the corner of his eye, he saw Ron crawling towards him. There was a manic glint in his blue orbs, one that reminded him so much of Hermione in her exam fever.

“Keep talking,” he said, shaking Harry by the neck of his shirt.

His spectacles askew, he tried repositioning them and licked his lips, tasting the last drops of Firewhisky. He smacked Ron’s hand, then rolled over and placed his palms under his head. Harry closed his eyes and tried to remember what happened next.

“Then we did it,” he said, squinting to stop the universe crushing onto him.

“Blimey, I bet you didn’t even last long enough,” Ron muttered, rolling the way Harry did and mimicking his position. Both boys were sprawled on the Burrow’s floor, the world whirling and twirling before their eyes.

“I did!” Harry blurted out, hurt in his masculine pride. He didn’t stop to think about it, but now that he did, he was quite delighted with himself. It had been very much enjoyable for both of them, he assured himself. It had been great, splendid even, right? Right?

“What did she say?” Ron asked, touching his elbow to his friend’s.

“That she loves me,” Harry declared, the animal in his chest roaring with pride.

“You’re dis-dis-disgusting,” the red-haired wizard stammered, seeing the ceiling come closer to him now.

“And you’re a git,” Harry pointed out. “And I love her. In fact, I’m quite barmy” he said, swinging an arm over his eyes and knocking his glasses aside in the process. He was positive he might vomit if he kept staring at the revolving ceiling.

A moment of silence stretched between the two drunken lads. Neither wanted to barf in front of the other, for that would mean losing the testosterone contest that had ensued between them. It was adamant that they hold on as tightly as possible and may the best man win.

“Mate?” Ron tried speaking; he felt that his tongue weighted a tone and the sheer effort of using it to articulate words was taking away his last amount of energy.

“Yeah?” Harry replied, his eyes in danger of rolling to the back of their sockets.

“What – y’know,” he tried moving his lips, but they didn’t quite comply. “What position did you use?”

At this, Harry jumped to his feet, which was a very bad idea in itself, especially when one takes into consideration the liter of Firewhisky digested by the eighteen year old mere minutes before. The walls came crashing into him and he plummeted back to the ground, nearly giving Ron a black eye in the process.

“Spit it out, you bloody wanker,” the younger Weasley tried sounding serious, dangerous, but to no avail. His only response was Harry choking on his own saliva while laughing and specifying that he’d never been called a wanker before. In truth, they’d never actually been this hammered before.

“I’m fucking serious, mate. You won’t see me running to George for advice. Oh, piss off!” he shoved a very amused Harry.

“Fine, fine,” he heaved. “I’ll tell you,” he added between chuckles. Ron propped his head up and stared at him with as much interest as someone in his state could.

“I think they call it the miss-narry,” Harry explained with an air of importance, butchering the word.

“The what?” Ron interrogated, leaning down over Harry to better hear his maudlin answer.

“The miss-narry,” he said again, a little spit coming out of his mouth. He wiped it with the tips of his fingers and flipped his form to face Ron. “It’s when she’s laying on her back and you get on top,” he continued his report and his friend nodded in acknowledgement.

“Bollocks,” Ron hiccupped.“Anything else, then?” he asked, slightly pouting.

“No, mate, wha’s wrong with’ya?” Harry’s head slipped from its support in utter shock.

“I mean, was that all?”

“Whaddya mean?!” Harry spat. “What else was I supposed to do?”

Fear started clawing at his tipsy heart. What if he completely failed Ginny? What if she hated him now? What if she thought he couldn’t even satisfy her? Shame started mingling with fear and alcohol, and he wanted to bang his head on the floor as many times as he needed to lose consciousness. All of a sudden, being awake felt extremely painful.

“Dunno, I just imagined you’d be up all night – you know – heavily…shagging,” Ron scratched his forehead, banishing his bangs from his eyes.

“Yeah, right,” Harry exhaled in a spontaneous fit of honesty. “You’re lucky if you can hold it for ten minutes,” he grunted, collapsing on his back again.

“You mean…hold it up?”

Harry screamed with mirth. At least, he had no problem with that. Oh no, he considered himself to be excelling at this particular aspect, thankyouverymuch. Opening his eyes, he recognized a blurred Ron hovering above him.

“Gerrof!” he wailed, trying to push his best friend off him. “What the actual fuck?” he asked, poking Ron in the chest.

“I’ll pretend it’s not my little sister we’re talking about if you give me more details. Did you give her the ol’ Aussie kiss, because I was close to doing it to Hermione, but then –“

“Ron, Hermione’s like my sister, you can’t tell me that!” Harry pressed both palms to his eyes, trying to get rid of the mental image of his two best mates starkers, going down on each other. “You’re positively mad,” he concluded, disregarding the fact that nothing but a deep state of ebriety would determine Ron to pry into his sister’s - and his very own - private affairs, begging for details.

“She’s not your sister, you berk. Her name is Granger, you are Potter,” the redheaded boy justified, employing a tone close to what Harry used when talking to Teddy.

“I said like my sister,” he sighed. “I did, though,” Harry slightly grinned and Ron’s mouth opened in amazement. The raven-haired boy acted as though he was confessing he could perform the Wronski feint with his eyes closed, and he felt chuffed to bits.

Ron marveled at how experienced his best friend was, when he thought him more ignorant than his own self. Bloody hell, Harry was awful with women, that much he always reckoned. It was one of the few areas where he didn’t outshine Ron. And he, Ron Weasley, was still ignorant by circumstance, not by his own will, if he had to admit. Nevertheless, this was a heavenly chance to shed his ignorance and take a step closer to becoming a man. In his own woozy mind, at least.

“Is-t c-complicated?” he stumbled, words melting into each other.

“Nah. Tell you what, when you get to it, call for me and I’ll Apparate there to offer you the necessary instructions,” Harry patted his friend on the shoulder and instantly burst into laughter.

“Piss off,” Ron shot, sincerely disappointed.

Hours later, when Mr and Mrs Weasley stepped out of the green flames and into their usually tidy kitchen, they almost stomped on two very drunk boys. Their own son and their almost son were snoring loudly, having fallen asleep into each other’s arms. Two chairs were kicked to the ground and the remnants of the Ogden’s Old Firewhisky bottle drenching the wooden floor.

“Dear, I think it’s time we took out the hangover potion once again,” Mr Weasley gently told his wife, who was currently at a loss for words. Her eyes were throwing daggers at the two unlucky teens and her husband turned around to smile. He was familiar with the storm which was about to come and he’d make sure to have some business as far away as possible. This was definitely not the first time they were greeted by whisky-soaked snores. He rapidly reminisced the younger versions of Bill and Charlie slouched under the kitchen table in pretty much the same fashion. Of course, Fred and George had been too precocious in their alcoholic adventures, as they’d been in all shenanigans. And there had been that one incident with Percy not so long ago. Indeed, the Weasley house had never been shy of men and their antics.

A shower of ice cold water emitted from the matron’s wand brought the wasted blokes to their feet, teeth chattering and spitting out blasphemies.

“Ronald. Bilius. Weasley!” Arthur Weasley heard the dulcet tones of his wife’s voice before he took refuge in his old garage, chuckling.

Chapter End Notes

I will never get over the fact that, whenever they have this conversation, they are actually talking about each other's sister. Awkwardness alert! Anyway, bless them, they're so adorable!

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page

Homerun

fightfortherightsofhouseelves

previous page next page

breaktime

Chapter Summary

Finally, they had time.

Chapter Notes

two years ago i was wishing wonderful blvnk a happy birthday by publishing a new chapter of what was already a story entirely inspired by her breathtaking art.
it only made sense that i returned to create a new sequel on her 26th :)

happy birthday, lovely! take your time and do things in your own way, life isn't rushing anywhere <3

See the end of the chapter for more notes

She didn’t feel like getting out of bed so soon, Harry noticed, pleased. He didn’t either.

It had been nearly four long months without her, almost a hundred and twenty days without feeling her skin warm against his, without touching his lips to hers, without tasting her. Yes, it had been too long and they both agreed making up for it was top priority.

They’d been writing back and forth all throughout Ginny’s final year at Hogwarts, hearts beating fast and pulse strumming up at any slight flutter of owlish wings. Thus, after the disastrous encounter from Easter, they sensibly concluded and agreed upon during their assiduous letter exchange, that it was time Harry left the safety of the Burrow for some more private and definitely less crowded (read: brotherless) quarters. And Ginny’d swiftly join him once out of Hogwarts.

The plan was carefully thought and designed to work out swimmingly, had it not been for Mrs Weasley (who, naturally, had a different idea of what was appropriate for her freshly graduate daughter). Nevertheless, the shouting and harrumphing did little to stop Ginny from storming out of the Burrow as soon as she’d clobbered her luggage through the door of her room and announced that there was no need for the family to wait for her as she would be spending the weekend with Harry.

The little show left Harry more than a bit befuddled and standing stupidly in the middle of the Burrow’s living room, feeling the full intensity of the combined stares of Ron, George, and Bill. Mr Weasley though, he was peacefully perusing the day’s copy of the Prophet, horn-rimmed spectacles perched on the tip of his nose and small ahas escaping his lips once every few minutes as if the information he was absorbing was nothing short of spectacular.

Therefore Ginny found it sensible to let out all her family related pent up frustration once she was finally alone with Harry in his newly rented one bedroom apartment near the Leaky Cauldron; which mostly resulted in a heated and rough session on Harry’s shabby old couch, coffee table and nearest wall - not that Harry was complaining in any way. Far from that actually (and shoving aside the feeling of guilt Ron’s scornful stare had inflicted upon him), he made a point to give her his best moves and whatever stamina a soon to be twenty year old could summon. Twice.

It was precisely how it was possible that he found himself blissfully in bed on an early July morning, enjoying the pure quiet of dawn, Ginny lounged half naked over him, arms pulling him snug and close to her. The timid daylight caught in her hair, setting a gentle glow about it and illuminating the white of her skin, the freckles burned into it resembling little colour spots flicked haphazardly by a masterful painter on a blank canvas.  It was peaceful.

He’d grown a beard since they’d last seen each other, got a haircut and an increased dose of confidence in bed. Ginny was delighted to notice all three aspects, each leaving her more thirsty for him than the other.

She’d bitten her lips when the Hogwarts Express rolled into King’s Cross and she jumped off the lolling wagon and into his arms, tracing her fingers through his beard and then through his freshly trimmed locks. Cut, but still curling wildly at the back of his head, Ginny was pleased to notice.

And after they closed the door on the world and were finally, beautifully alone, Ginny was even more pleasantly surprised to register that the shy boy from the past summer who’s elbow kept bumping her or getting tangled in her hair when they made love was no longer there. Instead, she found a young man whose fingers did not tremble in the slightest when he undressed her, who didn’t blush even for a beat when his mouth traveled south down her body to remind her of another summer’s day - but this time without any hesitation or timidity. She found a young man who was no longer afraid of what he wanted when it came to her and it made her excited, aroused, insatiable.

Harry shivered when his mental recount of the previous night was interrupted by Ginny’s lips sweeping over his chest, kissing him gently, blearily up his collarbone, his neck. He smiled, traced his fingers through her hair and teased her with two fingers running down the length of her arm. It always gave her goosebumps when he did so and he could feel her breath catch if only for a heartbeat.

“Good morning,” Harry smirked against her forehead, kissed her there.

“Hello to you too,” she smiled and pressed her bare chest harder into him, pressed her cheek into his palm.

Feeling her breasts brush against his chest made Harry let out a brisk gasp, made his senses spike and fire up again. His eyes followed Ginny, down her bare, freckled back and lightly groaned when he saw the sheets sliding down her middle to her legs to reveal she’d been sleeping in a pair of his own pants.

He found that very, very sexy.

“Like what you see?” Ginny looked up at him and winked, sending a new tingling wave through Harry’s body.

He grinned, his hand dipping lower down her back and into her waistband, hooking one finger through it and pulling slightly.

“Where did you find these?”

“A girl never tells.”

Harry laughed at this display of mischief and wit and had a mind to tickle her until she told him exactly what she’d been up to (an interrogation tactic probably not approved by the Ministry, but who gave a damn) when she looked up at him intensely, opened her mouth and licked her lips.

“Don’t move,” Ginny instructed and, with a hand pressed to Harry’s chest, she lifted up on her knees and pushed her long, red hair back to one side.

Harry forgot what he’d planned on doing anyway. He stretched his hand and grasped for his glasses, mindlessly thrown away somewhere in the general vicinity of the bed amidst the heat of the previous night. At least he was certain he didn’t plan on missing the full and complete details of such a view.

Taking note of what he was doing, Ginny grinned and playfully tutted him, “You won’t be needing these, Mr Potter.”

His eyebrows raised into a questioning look, but Ginny simply batted her eyelashes at him and went about her business of slowly removing the pair of pants she’d been wearing, fully aware his eyes were glued to her.

“What’s going on in that devious mind of yours?” Harry smirked and tried to catch her in his arms; instead, Ginny pushed his hands away and, before he could protest, straddled him.

“Lay on your back. I’ve been thinking about something since last summer,” she instructed, pushing him back into the mattress with one soft palm.

Harry’s breath hitched. He licked his lips as his black messy head touched the white cotton sheets.

“That long?”

“Aha. So, you see, I’m pretty anxious to start.”

Her voice was loaded with mischief and Harry groaned hard. His fists gripped the sheets beneath him as he felt Ginny inching closer to him, her thighs brushing past his arms, his shoulders to finally rest on either side of his face and be tickled by the rugged hairs of his beard.

“Ready?” She asked, her eyes intently on his.

Harry could only nod.

Parting her legs wider, she grasped a handful of his hair and leaned slowly on his face. He raised his palms to her lower back and held her there.

Ginny moaned when Harry opened his mouth beneath her and let out a warm breath. She could feel her stomach churn and an ever-growing fire climbing up from her center to her chest.

Her head shot back once his tongue tasted her, sliding over the inside of her inner walls until it reached a little bundle of nerves and pressed into it.

“Harry, please,” she moaned louder, fist gripping harder into his hair.

Harry understood precisely what she was asking him. During Ginny’s Easter break, they’d taken their time to learn, to truly grasp what each other liked, needed, and wanted. Snuggled together under a blanket on Ginny’s bed, they thought it was the perfect time to repeat everything they’d been doing since the previous summer, but slower and following each other’s instructions. To them, it was their time to discuss what felt good and teach each other how to make the experience even better for both of them.

Unfortunately, and through some bizzare chain of events, none of them remembered to properly lock the door - which, as one can imagine, led to a rather embarrassing situation involving Ron standing at the entrance, cheeks and ears flaming red, looking as though he’d been slapped over the face, Ginny cursing like a sailor and Harry regretting that Voldemort didn’t do a better job at trying to murder him.

Even if their actual actions were concealed from Ron’s prying eyes by the blanket, neither Harry nor Ginny believed he didn’t understand or at least guessed that they weren’t merely holding hands. In all honesty, Ron had opened the door as Ginny was begging Harry not to stop and to “keep going exactly like that.”

Ginny was right, Harry had thought then, Ron did have a knack for interrupting people at the worst possible time.

But it was that stolen afternoon when he learned how Ginny liked to be touched, her ragged breath and “Harry, please” reverberating through his brain endlessly over the past months, torturing his mind every single day of the one hundred and twenty that lay ahead of them back then.

“Please,” Ginny murmured again, arching her back and pressing deeper into his mouth.

Harry felt himself pulsing, already too hard, too aroused. He tightened his grip around her lower back and pushed her further down into him, his tongue moving round in circles inside her.

He didn’t stop: not when she spread her legs wider still, not when his own hand slid inside his boxers to take the edge off if only for a small moment, not when he dug so deep inside, tongue bouncing around her clit in heavier and heavier rotations that she screamed and pushed lower into his face. Harry didn’t stop. He wanted her to feel bloody good.

Ginny thrust her pelvis onto him fastly, urgently, hand still gripping his hair for balance. Her thighs rubbed against his cheeks with each thrust, her long hair tickled his chest as she arched her back. He could feel she was close.

He removed the hand he kept on himself and moved it to cup under her arse. With both hands, Harry grabbed her and held her perfectly still over his face. Let me finish this, don’t move, was what he wanted to say. She understood.

Ginny pushed into his tongue as it started moving faster, licking and drinking the heath inside her. It took her only a couple more strokes before she felt she could let go.

“Harry,” Ginny cried his name and froze on top of him as she felt countless waves of pleasure wash over her body, obliviate her mind.

Harry dashed his tongue over her twice more before he let her sink next to him, heaving and panting, one arm over her eyes.

“Alright, Gin?” He asked, kissing her elbow, her arm, her wrist.

“Oh, yeah, I’m only taking a moment to congratulate myself for having this idea,” she grinned, still panting, her eyes sparkling with love and mischief.

“Brilliant idea indeed,” Harry chuckled, pressing his lips to her temple, “I’d like to shake your hand for it.”

“Ha, I bet you would. But how about instead of shaking hands we took care of you too, eh?”

Harry took note of the naughty smile tugging at her lips and once again seemed to forget whatever he had planned on doing. He briefly decided that he’d just have to get accustomed to this superpower of hers that erased his mind and turned him into a sorry, mumbling puddle of a man.

Giggling, Ginny hooked her hands into his boxers and pulled down.

“Off with those, come on.”

Turning her back to him, she winked, inviting.

“I figured as long as we’re trying new things,” she said sweetly.

It was all the invitation he needed. Harry quickly jiggled the boxers off his ankles and onto the floor. Grinning excitedly, he crawled his way to Ginny and her beautiful, freckled back.

On his knees, Harry ran a hand up and down her back, over her spine and stopping to better feel her round, tight bum.

He gave himself a stroke and guided the tip forward, parting her. The moisture and heat at her entrance made him feel dizzy for a moment, a feeling akin to a blow to the back of his head.

Harry closed his eyes to gather himself; she drove him way beyond crazy and far away from any pretence of sanity.

“Tell me if I cock this up, yeah?” Harry whispered before he gently thrust and slid further inside her. He couldn’t help feeling a little bit anxious whenever they ventured on new territory.

“Just go hard and it’ll be brilliant.”

“Hard? You sure?”

“Yeah. And hold on to me tight.”

“Really?”

“And maybe pull my hair a little?”

“Oh, Gin, you’re not even giving me the chance to start, I’m already -”

“Here, let me.”

“Fuck.”

Soon enough, Harry felt himself let go, the violent tide so powerful it made him buckle over her, his hands squeezing her side, his teeth grazing the smooth skin of her back, her name on his lips like a secret prayer.

His heart beat so fast, his mind spinned and collided into millions of stars. Before his thoughts went blank, Harry found himself thinking that everything was too good, too happy to be true.

And what was even more incredible, the kind of good luck Harry wasn’t yet used to, was that they had a lifetime ahead to start again, to try new things, and practice. They were no longer rushing.

Finally, they had time.

Chapter End Notes

boy, isn't revisiting past stories a journey? my past tenses kept turning into present when i wasn't looking.
hope i did Homerun Harry and Ginny at least some justice. and now i'll leave them to enjoy their life together, they deserve it :)

please visit my tumblr for the link to the drawing that inspired this!

Table of contents

Preface
first base
second base
third base
fourth base|homerun
managerial ejection: a sequel
breaktime
Afterword

previous page start next page